Hello friends, Namaskar, today we are going to tell you about such
potential,
what is the explosion in To Protect Smart, what are the
reasons for you to not get the claim after paying the full premium under the term plan
and whatever cover you have taken thereafter, are there any reasons due to which
you cannot get the claim, this is the thing that
you should
read in your life after buying your Airtel plan, if
we keep all these things in mind then probably
we will not have any problem in getting the claim,
if we do not keep these things in mind then we will have
problem in getting it, after reading this from the company's side I am
telling you that no
such benefit for the benefit of the company will be given in respect of any listed condition
which is directly or proximately
caused by, however caused in consequence of, or
aggravated by any of the following,
pre-existing conditions or
conditions connected with pre-existing conditions will be excluded,
any pre-existing condition
for which the life insured had signs and
symptoms and it was diagnosed and
treated on the advice of a doctor within 48 months from the
date of issue of the policy or
between the period commenced on the date
of first unpaid premium till the date of inception
Excluded are: Any sexually transmitted
disease, STD and its related complications or
Presence of Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS) or any Human Neonatal Infection Virus (HNIV) Injury, Suicide, Insanity
and Deliberate participation of the life
assured in criminal acts, Drug
use, Alcoholism, Consumption of drugs other than those prescribed by the School of Yoga, Medical Practice,
War whether
declared or not, Civil commotion, Violation of
criminal law, Invasion, Hostility where war has been declared, Rebellion, Revolution, Warfare, Invas ...
Any treatment of the donor due to
birthday
fraud or illness Any disease which has appeared or been diagnosed
before the life assured attaining the age of 17 years
Death
Benefit Very easy option Monthly income will be
payable electronically only Tax Benefits
Tax under the policy is subject to Section 80 of the Income Tax Act, 1968
Service tax and cess, if applicable, will be applicable
as per the applicable rates Tax
laws are subject to amendment from time to time
Anticipation of Suicide If the life assured, whether sane or insane, commits
suicide within one year from the date of inception of this policy, the
nominee or beneficiary shall be entitled to
eighty per cent of the premiums paid on death
Provided that the policy is in force in case of a
Limited Pay or Regular Pay policy,
if the life assured,
whether sane or insane, commits
suicide within one year from the date of inception of this policy, the
nominee or beneficiary shall be entitled to
eighty per cent of the premiums paid till the date of death. The
surrender period available at the time of death shall be
15 days grace period for payment of premiums on
monthly premium
payment  The grace period is
applicable for 30 days for other modes of premium payment.
If the premium is not paid within the grace period, the
party will be dissolved and the cover will be discontinued.
Limited Payment Option Premium must be paid
only for the chosen premium payment form. The
PIL CIA benefit will remain valid for the policy term after the premium is deposited for the policy term.
Premium Waiver: If the premium is paid
late or the premium is
not paid within the grace period,
all benefits under this policy will be discontinued.
Term Revival: A Parsi
who has already paid the premium can be
appealed for revival within 2 years from the date of prepaid end of TRP
and the date of policy
repayment. Revival will be followed by the
Board appointed under the Policy Wellbeing. The
policy will be recommended for revival by the Policy Wellbeing Board.
Satisfactory proof of health of the life assured as
required by the previous BUA team. Underwriting Payee
for CIA Chief Benefit:
3 months waiting period for approved benefit
after 3 months.  The waiting period
for any revival within 3 months of the first unpaid premium will
not be applicable.
Any change in the redemption conditions will be
subject to prior approval from IRDA and will be
disclosed to the policy holders. The
basis for calculation of surrender value will be reviewed from time to time
and factors applicable to the existing business may be included in the policy.
Nomination Requirements Nomination in the policy should be made
under Section 395 of the Insurance Laws (
Amendment) Act, 2015 as amended from
time to time.
For more details on this section please
visit our website. Requirements of Slice AB Silent
Assignment in the policy is governed by
Section 38 of the Insurance Laws (Amendment) Act, 2015 as amended from
time to time.
For more details on this section please visit our website. Section 41 As per
Section 41 of the Insurance Laws (Amendment) Act, 2015 as
amended from time to time, no
person shall directly or indirectly offer to offer
or allow
any person to assign any insurance in India  No person shall take out, renew or continue any insurance in respect of
any kind of risk relating to life insurance property on the basis of commission nor shall he induce
any person to take out,
renew or continue any insurance policy
or to accept any rebate of the whole or part of the premium shown on any insurance policy
except such rebate as may be
allowed in accordance with the published schedule of insurance companies:
Provided that the acceptance by an insurance agent of commission in
respect of a policy of life insurance taken out by him on his life shall not be accepted as a rebate of premium
within the meaning of this section provided the acceptance by the insurance
agent is subject to the
conditions that
he is an insurance agent employed by the insurance company. Any person making default in
complying with the provisions of this section shall be punishable with fine which may extend to ₹
10,000,000. The offences of fraud and misrepresentation shall be punishable with fine which may extend to ₹10,000,000. Such offences shall also be punishable with fine which may extend to ₹10,000,000. The offences of fraud
and misrepresentation shall also be punishable with fine which may extend to ₹10,000,000. The offences of fraud and misrepresentation shall also be punishable with fine which may extend to ₹10,000,000. The offences of fraud
and misrepresentation shall also be punishable with
fine which may extend to ₹5 lakh.  The
CI benefit on the Buktan of Plasty
is more than Rs. 25 lakhs. It will continue
for other CIAs with weakness I love by Plant Sinus Plasty. The
specific seal will be reduced proportionately in future for you.
All the premiums mentioned above are included in the plan
and up to Rs. 2 crore. Accidental Death Benefit is
available in one option in Accidental Death Loan.
Critical Illness ES is paid to the subscriber and in case of
critical illness and death problem, the CID benefit equal to the closed loop will terminate on the Buktan of Plasty. Only doctor's certificate confirming the diagnosis has to be submitted. If the direct benefit on the Buktan of Plasty is more than Rs. 5 lakhs. The direct benefit on the
Buktan of Plasty is less than Rs. 5 lakhs. The direct benefit on the Buktan of Plasty will continue for other CIAs with weakness I love by Plant Sinus Plasty. The specific seal will be reduced proportionately for you in future. All the premiums mentioned above are included in the plan and up to Rs. 2 crore. Accidental Death Benefit is available in one option in Accidental Death Loan. Critical Illness ES is paid to the subscriber and in case of critical illness and death problem, the benefit will terminate on the Buktan of Plasty. Only
doctor's certificate confirming the
diagnosis has to be submitted. The
direct benefit on the Buktan of Plasty is more than Rs.
5 lakhs. The direct benefit on the Buktan of Plasty is less than Rs. 5 lakhs. The direct benefit on the Buktan of Plasty is
continued for other CIAs with weakness I love by Plant Sinus Plasty. The specific seal will be reduced proportionately for you in future. To
know more about the diseases covered,
please visit Place Rochelle.
View the area available under Life and Health and
Allied
A in one option.  ICICI Prudential Life Insurance is a top selling service based
on the number of policies sold online between 2016 and
February 2017.
Plan Viewers are the top selling service for plans that are
purchased by customers through our website via Zero Paper
Process 52 ICICI Prudential iProtect
Smart has been voted Product of the Year 2016
in the Consumer Survey of Product Innovation in the Life Insurance category in
a survey of over 7000 people by Nielsen.
Paralysis for terminal illness will cease on the discontinuance of this benefit.
Nothing contained herein shall
operate to destroy or abridge the right of any creditor to be
paid out of the proceeds of any policy of the assured who may have been
affected by the appeal of the assured unless it is
otherwise taken to be in order to defraud the creditor.
In case of any third party claim in the Courts of India in respect of the insurance proceeds, the amount shall be
subject to the directions of the judiciary. Please seek
professional legal advice for the applicability of this provision.
Service tax and kickbacks will be
levied additionally as per prevailing tax under Act 1968 by APTC Ltd. However, the law is
subject to amendment from time to time. Subject to payment and
receipt of documents, the claim figures are
for the financial year 2017-18 and
based on the calculations, the
total individual claims for the financial year have been
calculated. This is to be rewritten for
public disclosure on our website for depot style.
Friends, you may be
aware of this exclusion made by me.
You may or may not understand it very well,
but friends, try to
understand it. If you liked the information given by me
and my video, then
like, share, subscribe and
friends,
press the bell icon notification button for my next video and then turn
it on so that whatever video
I make next, it reaches you immediately.
Friends, if you like my video, then do like it so that there is
enthusiasm in making my next video. Friends, if you want to get
any information about this plan, then
call me
on my phone.  You can call me or you
can like and comment on my channel that you
want to talk to me, you can leave your phone number,
my mobile number is 10291 2080
Friends, if you like the information given by me, then
please share,
type, like, thank you, my
friends
Hello friends, in the end I will definitely say one thing, if
you do not understand anything in this, then
please read the Shells Professor carefully, it is
possible that I might have made some mistakes in speaking,
please take care of this thing,
thank you
Jhal